Sharad Bhardwaj

Digital Marketing Executive

PHONE:+91-9649913379

EMAIL:Sharad3379@gmail.com

Summary

Self-Motivated and technology enthusiast, with the skillset complementing exploration and learning.

1 year and 7 months of experience in marketing space. Which helped to establish a good understanding of modern marketing trends. From this position, I seek opportunities to learn new skills for the progress of the company as well as individually.

- On and off-page SEO
- PPC
- Backlink generation.
- Organic lead generation
- •Lead generation through email campaigns, website, and

Social media promotion.

- •Keyword Research with trending topics.
- Marketing strategy planning and implementation.
- Email marketing.
- •Well-versed with domains like SaaS, Semiconductors and Medical Devices

Skills

Digital Marketing, SEO

Content Marketing, Social Media, Pay Per Click (PPC), Basics of Google Ads. Google Analytics, Online Marketing, Google Search Console, Keyword Planning, Search Engine Marketing (SEM), Conversion Rate Optimization. Marketing, Email, Sendinblue, Hubspot, Keyword Research

Currently Working

Pacifica Companies
E-Marketing Executive
Dec 2020 - Present

Experience

SoftwareSuggest

Digital Marketing Executive May 2019 - Sept.2020 (1yr. 4months)

Modern Insulators Pvt. Ltd. Trainee Engineer in Production Dept. August 2018 - April 2019 (9 months)

Education

- B.Tech. (Mechanical Engineering) (74.4%)
- Diploma in Mechanical Engineering with 62.76%
- Completed 10th from RBSE with48%

Hobbies

Driving

Watching Movies and Standup Comedy